[{"QN":"1","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What are the inputs for Portfolio planning?","A":" Initial release plan","B":" Newly envisioned product idea from product planning","C":" A sprint backlog","D":" All above","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":"  "},{"QN":"2","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What are outputs of Product-level planning?","A":" The product vision that provides a clear description of the areas in which the stakeholders get value","B":" To generate an initial high-level version of the product backlog","C":" To build a product roadmap that communicates the incremental nature of how the product will be built and delivered over time","D":" All above","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"  ","_7":""},{"QN":"3","Type":"MCQ","Question":"In Product planning, product backlog items included the following:","A":" Detailed user stories","B":" Epic-level user stories","C":" Tasks","D":" All above","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"  ","_7":""},{"QN":"4","Type":"MCQ","Question":"The Product roadmap communicates following:","A":" The incremental nature of how the product will be built","B":" How product will be delivered over time","C":" The important factors/constraint that drive each individual release.","D":" All above","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"5","Type":"MSQ","Question":"Release planning includes :(Select Multiple Answers)","A":" Budget trade-offs for incremental deliveries","B":" Task break down","C":" Release Date","D":" Product vision","E":" Deciding scope","F":"","CorrectOption":"A C E","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"6","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Why does scrum favor smaller, more frequent releases?","A":" To provide faster feedback","B":" To improve a product’s return on investment (ROI)","C":" Because the initial smaller release can becomes so small as to not be marketable","D":" All the above","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"7","Type":"MCQ","Question":"At what stage , Release planning is done?","A":" During Portfolio planning","B":" Before starting the first sprint","C":" Daily","D":" All above","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"8","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Sprint Backlog is :","A":" Backlog items that the Scrum team will work on in the next sprint","B":" The team generates a sprint backlog","C":" Occurs at the beginning of each sprint","D":" A description of the task-level work that has to be completed","E":" Just in time detailed planning","F":" All above","CorrectOption":"F","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"9","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Follow is true for Daily stand-up meeting:","A":" The most detailed level of planning occurs during the team’s daily scrum meeting","B":" The team members get together and each person takes turns stating what they got done since the last daily scrum","C":" What they are planning to work on today","D":" Whether they have any impediments","E":" All above","F":"","CorrectOption":"E","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"10","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Portfolio planning has following outputs:","A":" The portfolio backlog, which is a prioritized list of future products","B":" New products that have been approved and are ready for immediate development","C":" The products that are currently in process and have been approved to continue","D":" All above","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"11","Type":"MSQ","Question":"Who are the Stakeholders?(Select Multiple Answers)","A":" Company Share holders","B":" SMEs","C":" Investors","D":" Have a Say in your project/product","E":" Pre-Sales Team","F":" People sitting in tax-havens (like canary islands, etc)","CorrectOption":"B D E","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"12","Type":"MSQ","Question":"Why Stakeholders engagement is important?(Select Multiple Answers)","A":" To obtain regular feedback on Project progress/increment","B":" At some point, you will need to give bad news","C":" To keep Stakeholders happy","D":"","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"A B","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"13","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Stakeholders feedback is important because :","A":" Based on the feedback, the product owner and team can alter both what they plan to work on next","B":" How the team plans to do the work","C":" Frequent feedback to ensure that the right product is built","D":" To ensure the product is built right","E":" All above","F":"","CorrectOption":"E","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"14","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Ways to Engage Your Stakeholders:","A":" A Requirements Workshop","B":" Brainstorming Sessions","C":" Interviews","D":" Questionnaires","E":" All above","F":"","CorrectOption":"E","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"15","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Responsibilities of Stakeholders:","A":" Remain engaged from the definition to the completion of the Epic","B":" Provide ongoing feedback and support","C":" Contribute to the growth of a trusting Agile environment","D":" Define and clarify requirements","E":" Collaborate with the Product Owner","F":" All above","CorrectOption":"F","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"16","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Why we need Agile team charter?","A":" Project vision needs to documented","B":" To establish command and control","C":" Unwritten Team Rules are not enough","D":" To prioritize the product backlog","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"C","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"17","Type":"MSQ","Question":"Which among the below is true about the Agile charter?(Select Multiple Answers)","A":" Timely and Succinct","B":" Realistic","C":" Fixed","D":" Team-created","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"A B D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"18","Type":"MCQ","Question":"","A":"","B":"","C":"","D":"","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"19","Type":"MCQ","Question":"","A":"","B":"","C":"","D":"","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"20","Type":"MCQ","Question":"","A":"","B":"","C":"","D":"","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"21","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Which type of planning provides flexibility & adaptability in the overall project life cycle?","A":" Predictive planning","B":" Adaptive planning","C":"","D":"","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B","":"  ","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"22","Type":"MSQ","Question":"Why frequent replanning is favored in Adaptive planning?(Select Multiple Answers)","A":" To validate our assumptions","B":" To continuously produce better, more useful plans","C":" We worry about our plans being wrong","D":" To replace them with more accurate plans","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"A B D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"23","Type":"MSQ","Question":"Benefits of Transparency(Select Multiple Answers)","A":" Increases Visualization","B":" Helps to control schedule","C":" Reduces Risk","D":" Helps to controls cost","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"A C","":"  ","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"24","Type":"MCQ","Question":"We strive for fast feedback because:","A":" Focus is on increasing learning","B":" Is vital for quickly uncovering and exploiting time-sensitive, emergent opportunities","C":" Fast feedback closes the learning loop quickly","D":" It is critical for helping truncate bad development paths before they can cause serious economic damage","E":" All above","F":"","CorrectOption":"E","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"25","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Agile Transparency is depicted through","A":" Artifacts: Project Vision Statement, Prioritized Product Backlog, Release Planning Schedule","B":" Meetings: Sprint Review Meetings, Daily Standup Meetings","C":" Information Radiators: Burndown Chart, Scrum board","D":" All of above","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"26","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Which of the following are the differences between Adaptive planning and Predictive planning?","A":" Architecture evolution","B":" Estimations timeframe","C":" Requirement prioritization","D":" All of above","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"27","Type":"MSQ","Question":"Adaptive planning is suitable when:(Select Multiple Answers)","A":" Changing or emerging requirements","B":" Stable Product backlog","C":" Fixed Scope","D":" Team is Growing","E":" Constant Customer Feedback","F":"","CorrectOption":"A D E","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"28","Type":"MSQ","Question":"When is most important use of burndown chart?(Select Multiple Answers)","A":" Forecast and Prediction","B":" Measuring speed of Team","C":" Progress against the plan","D":" Changes in scope","E":" Team efficiency","F":"","CorrectOption":"A C E","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"29","Type":"MSQ","Question":"Which of the following sentences are True for Adaptive Planning?(Select Multiple Answers)","A":" Planning is to create a detailed plan up front before development work begins.","B":" Up-front planning should be helpful without being excessive","C":" Find the proper balance between up-front prediction and just-in-time adaptation","D":" Keep planning options open until the last responsible moment","E":" All the above","F":"","CorrectOption":"B C D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"30","Type":"MSQ","Question":"Which of the following is True for Adaptive Planning?(Select Multiple Answers)","A":" Planning is to create a detailed plan up front before development work begins","B":" Find the proper balance between up-front prediction and just-in-time adaptation.","C":" Up-front planning should be helpful without being excessive.","D":" Keep planning options open until the last responsible moment","E":" All above","F":"","CorrectOption":"B C D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"31","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Which level of Adaptive planning determines which products to work on, in what order, and for how long?","A":" Product planning","B":" Release planning","C":" Strategy planning","D":" Portfolio planning","E":" Daily planning","F":"","CorrectOption":"D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"32","Type":"MCQ","Question":"A feedback loop steps are:","A":" Make an assumption (or set a goal)","B":" Build something (perform some activities)","C":" Get feedback on what was built","D":" Then use that feedback to inspect what was done relative to what was assumed","E":" All above","F":"","CorrectOption":"E","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"33","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What is the basis of Adaptive planning?","A":" A detailed up front planning","B":" Empirical roots of inspection and adaptation","C":" Do not produce any of the planning artifacts","D":" Requirements treated as of equal priority","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"B","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"34","Type":"MCQ","Question":"Which is the highest level of Adaptive planning?","A":" Daily planning","B":" Stake holder planning","C":" Portfolio planning","D":" Product planning","E":" Release planning","F":" Strategy planning","CorrectOption":"F","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"35","Type":"MSQ","Question":"Which of these are useful feedback tools and methods?(Select Multiple Answers)","A":" Burndown chart","B":" Kanban Board","C":" Metrics dashboard","D":" Team Happiness Index","E":" Powerepoint Presentation Slides","F":"","CorrectOption":"A B C D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":"36","Type":"MCQ","Question":"What are different levels of Feedback?","A":" Daily feedback","B":" Stakeholder's during Sprint review","C":" User feedback","D":" All above","E":"","F":"","CorrectOption":"D","":"","_1":"","_2":"","_3":"","_4":"","_5":"","_6":"","_7":""},{"QN":""}]